# Jenna Careri

508-932-1681 | jlcareri@comcast.net | Salt Lake City, UT | jennacareri.com

## summary

Adaptable UX designer with strong background in human-centered design and user research. Four years of experience leading content design for web and mobile applications in finance and ecommerce. Proven success collaborating with cross-functional teams and leadership to develop solutions that meet both business and user needs.

# projects

### eBay site-wide currency experience | jennacareri.com/ebay

- An end-to-end solution for currency exchange
- Worked with core team of four to conduct user research, articulate a design direction, and develop a seamless currency journey for buyers who shop across borders on eBay's global sites

#### Pocket Local travel app | jennacareri.com/pocketlocal

- A personalized experience, built for the way you already travel
- Researched and designed a new travel app to explore how it could be viable in a saturated market. Defined which user needs aren't currently met and what features a new app would require to make an impact.

#### Crossroads Urban Center redesign | jennacareri.com/crossroads

- A modern update for a local non-profit
- Designed a responsive website to increase confidence among possible donors and allow more
  effective volunteer scheduling. Developed bold, clear design direction focused on new user
  interface (UI) styles and reworked information architecture.

# relevant experience

## Senior Content Designer | eBay

#### Apr 2023 - Present | Salt Lake City, UT

- Lead content design for buyer payments, focused on user journey through cart and checkout
- Collaborate with research, product, and visual design partners to create global, site-wide single currency experience estimated to bring in \$9M in annual incremental revenue
- Design solutions for the unpaid items (UPI) initiative, including proactive collection of payment details, introduction of autopay, and buyer education to introduce the new experience

## Senior Content Designer | Wells Fargo

#### Nov 2021 - Dec 2022 | Salt Lake City, UT

- Designed web and mobile app features in the commercial and corporate banking division
- Refined voice and tone standards; developed guidelines and examples to inform the team's work

 Led content strategy for customer personas, working with core team to ensure personas are memorable and actionable

### **Content Designer | Red Ventures**

### November 2020 - November 2021 | Charlotte, NC

- Developed UX strategy for emails, user flows, and landing pages in the home services division
- Coordinated marketing copy across internal brands and an external partnership to ensure consistent brand messaging and voice
- Optimized web and mobile experiences with A/B tests, user research, and KPIs, leading to +144% in response rate on one project

## Copywriter | Red Ventures March 2019 - November 2020 | Charlotte, NC

## education

**Certificate in UX/UI** | University of Utah | Salt Lake City, UT | Expected Feb, 2024 Coursework includes: research practices, interaction design, heuristic evaluation, user persona development, information architecture (IA), decision mapping, storyboarding, wireframing and prototyping, and front-end development

**B.A., Journalism; B.A., French Studies** | University of Massachusetts Amherst | Amherst, MA | Summa cum laude

# skills

**UX/UI** | User research, agile methodology, visual and content strategy, journey mapping, style guide creation, persona development, information architecture

**Technical** | Jira, Figma, Invision, Asana, Stark, FullStory, Miro, WordPress, Google Analytics, Confluence, basic HTML/CSS

Language | French, fluent; English, native language